I remembered you — you're that beast.
That settled inside my head.
Now you'll be my substitute for glycine.
Don't resist; we will be friends.
I love you — you're that animal.
Warm, soft — I want to touch.
I want to feel something special.
Something prettier than a sick person's wheezing.
Someone sick, someone sick, someone sick.
Someone sick, someone sick.
I remembered you — you're that beast.
That settled inside my head.
Now you'll be my substitute for glycine.
Don't resist; we will be friends.
I love you — you're that animal.
Warm, soft — I want to touch.
I want to feel something special.
Something prettier than a sick person's wheezing.
Someone sick, someone sick, someone sick.
Someone sick, someone sick.